flight 370 after 3 days
飞行370后3天
Central Falls alarms the expanding search for the plane over water and now Land and what we learn about the passengers on board carrying stolen passports
中央瀑布报警扩大搜索面过水，现在土地和我们了解船上运载被盗护照的乘客是什么
without a trace how is it possible for a jumbo jet to disappear with no sign Force it's all about technology and there are limits
无踪怎么可能为一个大型喷气式客机消失，没有迹象强制它是所有关于技术和有限制
breaking his silence for the first time since that awful day in Newtown Connecticut the father of the gunman speaks out about his son and what he did
打破他的沉默，因为那可怕的一天在Newtown康涅狄格首次枪手的父亲讲了关于他的儿子和他做了什么
how it took a winner this severe to bring these sailors out of hibernation and back to Westport we really get to see that is not for the faint of heart
它是如何把一个赢家严重的，将这些水手的休眠状态，回到西港，我们真的能看到那个不适合心脏虚弱
nightly news begins now
晚间新闻现在开始
BBC News world headquarters is NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
BBC新闻全球总部是NBC​​晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
good evening tonight people the world over are asking the same question how is it possible that a jumbo jet has disappear without a trace
晚上好，今晚全世界人民都在问同样的问题怎么可能是一个大型喷气式客机已经消失的无影无踪
tonight the search has expanded over a large area for a large aircraft a Boeing triple 7 among the safest ever made this one with 239 souls on board
今晚的搜索已经扩大了大面积的大飞机波音三联7中最安全的有史以来与239灵魂上这一个
they were false alarms over the weekend of fuel slick on the water would look like an aircraft door but they didn't pan out and now because they have to chase down even the wildest possible theories the search continues on C and on land
他们是误报过的水燃料光滑的周末，看起来就像一个飞机舱门，但他们没有成功，现在，因为他们要追逐即使是最疯狂的可能的理论继续搜索C和土地上
incase this aircraft when on flying even though it left no electronic trail behind
柜面这架飞机在飞行上，即使它没有留下任何电子跟踪的背后
tonight the search is being conducted by 10 nations 34 Plains 48 vessels have been deployed in this
今晚的搜索是由10个国家34平原48艘进行已经部署在该
we begin our coverage tonight among are correspondence an expert domestically in overseas with NBC's Tom Costello Tom Green
我们开始我们今晚报道中都对应一个专家在国内与海外NBC的汤姆·科斯特洛汤姆·格林
hi Brian the nearest fax with a haven't found any trace of this plane yet is raising a possibility that they have been looking in the wrong place now a day break the search zone is expanding to also include the west coast of Malaysia and the waters of Indonesia
喜布莱恩最近的传真有没有发现这架飞机的任何踪迹又是提高的可能性，他们一直在寻找在错误的地方现在一天打破了搜索区域扩大到也包括马来西亚西海岸和海域印尼
Papa cost of Malaysia search for flight 370 has no interest 46 dozens of ships helicopters and planes in Vietnam
马来西亚寻找飞行370的爸爸成本并无计46数十种船舶和直升机在越南的飞机
nothing and oil sheen and debris spotted over the weekend ended up being falsely snow ski conditions are expected to worsen on board the USS Blue Ridge commander William marks
不信邪，油脂光泽和碎片发现在上周末结束了是假雪的滑雪条件预期恶化登上美国海军蓝岭号司令威廉·马克
that will make certain conditions more challenging about can't I use the car radars are all very advanced in a tax lien the gays allowed at surface clutter
这将使某些情况下约我不能使用汽车雷达都是非常先进的税收留置权的允许同性恋者在地面杂波更具挑战性
the last reported location for the bowling triple 7 was over the water halfway between Malaysia and Vietnam Malaysia military radar suggesting to play me off store to turn back the search zone is expanded to include Malaysia's mainland and now the water is to the northwest
对于保龄球三合一7上次报告的地点是马来西亚和越南马来西亚军用雷达提示打我关店回头搜索区域扩大到包括马来西亚的大陆，现在水是向西北间的水超过一半
Amanda questions tonight why would the plane turn back and why did my crew radio air traffic controllers a former senior NTSB investigator says a sudden loss of cabin pressure Griffin capacity of the crew and passengers within seconds will the plane continued flying
阿曼达问题今晚为什么会在飞机转回来，为什么我的船员无线电空中交通管制员一名前高级国家运输安全委员会调查员说的船员和乘客的客舱压力格里芬能在几秒钟内突然丧失将飞机继续飞
you really have to start looking at a trajectory path at a speed an altitude that they were at how far could this airplane go wealth corset had 7 & a half hours of fuel on it but you have to be realistic you have to come up with at least a rate of descent
你真的要开始看的轨迹路径的速度，高度，他们在多大程度上能这架飞机去丰富了紧身胸衣和7个半小时的燃料就可以了，但你必须，你必须拿出在成为现实的下降至少率
get the plane went down on land an emergency transmitter beacon should be sent
得到的飞机在陆地上的紧急信标发射机应该发送
what is a plane with down in the sea underwater pinger is attached to the black boxes should be sending a homing signal
什么是与在海中水下的声波发射器向下一个平面安装到黑盒应发送一个寻的信号
Duquesne C
杜肯Ç
Fox pinger of 8 in the water
8在水中福克斯萍儿
I want to act if they produce a brief Paul want a second for 30 days at a depth of up to 20000 feet
我想，如果它们产生一个简短保罗想要第二30天在高达20000英尺的深度，以充当
meanwhile the FBI is hoping to analyze the phone Prince of two individuals were thought would use a stolen European passports to board the plane Embassy justice course bonnet Pete Williams
与此同时，联邦调查局希望来分析两个人的手机王子被认为会用偷来的欧洲护照登机大使馆正义当然引擎盖皮特·威廉斯
businessman who used to live in Thailand baht the tickets for the two men that they say he wanted the cheapest fare possible that he did not mention any specific flight meaning of this man was from Iran US official say there is no indication so far this with terrorism again Alicia believe this
商人谁曾经住在泰国泰铢的门票两名男子，他们说他想要最便宜的票价有可能是他没有提到任何具体的飞行意思这个人是来自伊朗的美国官员说，没有迹象显示，到目前为止这与恐怖主义再次艾丽西亚相信这
plane have 7 hours of fuel or more still on board when it disappear to that greatly expanded the range of where this plane might be able to show p**** reports of a plane crash or debris
飞机有7小时燃料或以上仍在船上，当它消失了极大的扩展，其中这架飞机可能是能够显示飞机坠毁或碎屑的对****报告的范围
Tom Costello covers aviation for a starting a saw from RDC newsroom Tom Hanks as always in for more on this word join tonight by Greg Feith
汤姆·科斯特洛涵盖航空一开始从RDC编辑部汤姆汉克斯锯一如既往的为更多的关于这个词，今晚由格雷格·费斯加盟
what we saw and Tom species of Veteran Affairs investigations as a former senior Air Safety Director with the NTSB also happens to be a veteran pilot Greg you're in the business of ruling nothing out
我们所看到的和汤姆品种退伍军人事务部调查，作为一名前高级航空安全主任与国家运输安全委员会也恰好是一位资深的飞行员格雷格你在执政无中生有业务
the office were submitted as a Hollywood script projected for being too incredible if we're looking for this overland
办公室提交作为好莱坞的电影剧本预计为是太不可思议了，如果我们正在寻找这个陆路
doesn't that mean that were kind of theorizing it could have been a situation like a pro golfer Payne Stewart on board that small aircraft they were overcome by something in the air craft when on flying go in this case with no electronic trail
难道这不是意味着那种被理论化它可能是这样的情况一个职业高尔夫球手佩恩 - 斯图尔特登上小飞机，他们当上飞行的旅途在这种情况下，没有电子跟踪克服的东西在空中工艺
absolutely Bryan you bring up a good point with the fact that if this airplane have an explosive decompression incapacitated the crew
绝对布莱恩你带来了一个好点的事实，如果这架飞机有一个爆炸性减压无行为能力的船员
in the airplane was still capable of operating with autopilot airplane to continue on in any one of a number of track and that's why the search area
在飞机仍然能够与飞机自动驾驶仪操作，继续在一些轨道的任何一个的，这就是为什么搜索区域
got to be expanded to include land because it goes into the jungle Bella been to the dentist jungle and not releasing reveille we have a hole
得到扩大到包括土地，因为它进入丛林贝拉一直牙医丛林，而不是释放起床号，我们有一个孔
porn on this later in the broadcast R Us frustrated by the limits of Technology in this day in age as we civilians are
色情这个后来在广播玩具反斗城通过技术在这一天的年龄限制沮丧，因为我们是平民
absolutely Bryan we had this discussion over the years in the industry now there is new technology that is being incorporated in their planes called
我们多年来在行业中的磨砺过这样的讨论绝对布莱恩现在有是在他们的飞机被纳入新的技术，称为
B or automated a dependent surveillance broadcast it is GPS it is updating once every second with a lot of information but it isn't mandated
B或一个自动相关监视广播它是全球定位系统正在更新一次，第二次用了大量的信息，但它不强制
universally around the world right now
普遍世界各地，现在
grade 5 TSP thank you very much for being with us again tonight for the families of the missing on flight 370 as you can imagine this has been an awful few days imagine not having a shred of information about a family member on that flight
5年级的TSP非常感谢你的再次和我们今晚上飞行370失踪者的家属，你可以想像这一直是一个可怕的几天想象没有关于该航班的家庭成员信息一丝一毫
NBC skier Simmons is at the airport in Kuala Lumpur where flight 370 originated from here
NBC滑雪者西蒙斯是在机场吉隆坡航班地方370从这里发源
5370 have been waiting for this Apple how many days now but not just here anymore have been waiting in Beijing Vehicross final destination
5370一直在等待这个苹果有多少天，但现在不只是在这里了已经等在北京Vehicross最终目的地
missing plane
飞机失踪
relations online
网上关系
Chinese woman Asians including 3 from the United States Phillip Buda Texas what for IBM is brothers set on today just recently been hungry for a visit it was
中国女人的亚洲人，包括3来自美国菲利普布达得克萨斯什么IBM是兄弟今天仅有最近一直饿了访问它
gift that we didn't get to Sam
礼物，我们没有得到山姆
whole week and we got to spend some quality time eating
整整一个星期，我们得花一些时间吃
you know a dinner or together
你知道吃饭或一起
meaning Ching lived in Pittsburgh neighbors are heartbroken I've been crying since I got the song called a few stand with boobs on the flight cancelled at the last minute
意清住在匹兹堡的邻居都伤心欲绝，我一直哭，因为我得到了这首歌叫了几个立场上取消在最后一分钟的飞行胸部
are considered the absolute providence of God by the grace of God I was not on that plane
都是神的恩典，我是不是该考虑平面神的绝对天意
Turnbull and prayers are answered
特恩布尔和祈祷得​​到了回应
like we plan to join a very search and rescue Akron over the ocean looking for clues Bryant of exactly what happened
像我们计划加入一个非常搜救阿克伦的海洋寻找线索到底发生了什么科比
Simmons in Kuala Lumpur in again later on the broadcast a special look at the frustrations of Technology here now to watch men are top story here much are the last two weeks the ongoing crisis in Ukraine
西蒙斯在吉隆坡再后来就广播一个特殊的看科技的挫折这里来观看的人都是顶级的故事在这里多的是过去两个星期的持续危机在乌克兰
there were shots fired at a Ukrainian naval post in Crimea region today report say unidentified man fired into the air before then taking over the face
有枪射向乌克兰海军后在克里米亚地区今天报告说，身份不明的男子朝天开枪之前，然后采取在脸上
is the latest confrontation Sons Russian military group seized control of the peninsula
是最新的父子对抗俄军缴获组半岛的控制权
meanwhile today NATO announce table start reconnaissance
今天同时宣布，北约表起始侦察
flights to the south and west monitor
飞往南部和西部显示器
Ukrainian border with a wax aircraft Ukraine is not a NATO member but Russia's actions have alarm countries that are part of the Alliance and were once part of the Soviet Union
用蜡飞机乌克兰乌克兰边境不是北约成员国，但俄罗斯的行动也属于联盟的一部分，报警的国家和曾经是苏联的一部分
we turn out of Syria where the brutal Civil War is about to enter its fourth year and where the devastating tall is being felt especially hard by the children caught up in the conflict the new reporter says over 4 million children need humanitarian assistance
我们打​​开了叙利亚所在的残酷内战即将进入第四个年头，并在那里的破坏性高大的被感觉到特别困难者陷入了冲突的新记者说，超过400万儿童需要人道主义援​​助的儿童
once more than 1 million have fled the neighboring countries tonight as we kick off a series of reports on the forgotten children in this war in Syria
一旦超过1万人逃到邻国今晚我们揭开序幕了一系列在这场战争中被遗忘的孩子在叙利亚报告
are chief medical editor Dr Nancy Snyderman is made her way to Lebanon just across the border she's a hospital caring for the youngest of these victims Nancy good evening
正在首席医学编辑南茜斯奈德曼博士是由她的方式向黎巴嫩刚刚越过边境，她是一个有爱心的医院为这些年轻的受害者南希晚上好
good evening decimation to the hospital structure in Syria and that's one more reason why a small 32 best hospital with 27 incubators Wichita Craigslist
晚上好抽取到医院结构在叙利亚，这就是一个原因与孵化器27威奇托的Craigslist为什么一个小32最好的医院
mothers are getting a prenatal vitamins
母亲得到一个产前维生素
preterm delivery of babies are very vulnerable in the last date of birth defects residency when I was a pediatric healthcare crisis
婴儿早产是非常脆弱的出生缺陷居住的最后一天，当我还是个儿科医疗保健危机
Texas soon as it was as a global serious going to be right now 18 percent
德州很快，因为它是作为一个全球性的严重的将是现在的18％
cross the border are seen at the hospital bulging at the scene where is going to take you find the scenes of the hospital in surrounding refugee camps France
过关被视为在医院鼓鼓的场面是要带你找医院的场景，周围的难民营法国
for a first-time luck with amazing access to highlight the Forgotten of this war Syria children Ryan
对于首次运气惊人的访问突出忘记这场战争的叙利亚儿童瑞恩
Dr Nancy Snyderman who was made her way to Lebanon Dr Schneiderman think you are series of reports starts tomorrow morning on today in across all the broadcast on platforms of NBC News
谁是做她的方式向黎巴嫩医生SCHNEIDERMAN以为你是系列报道南希斯奈德曼开始医生明天早上就在今天在所有播出的NBC新闻平台
in this country nfen 15 months in Saigon man walked in the Sandy Hook Elementary School in Newtown Connecticut and started shooting in classrooms that were full of 6 & 7 year old before killing himself
在这个国家NFEN在西贡男子15个月走在桑迪胡克小学在Newtown康涅狄格州，并开始在爆满的6和7岁的自杀前拍摄的教室
tonight for the first time we are getting new insights into Adam Lanza from his father Peter who spoke with journalist an author Andrew Solomon for an article in this week's New Yorker magazine
今晚是第一次，我们从他的父亲彼得谁与记者的作者安德鲁·所罗门讲了在本周的纽约人杂志的一篇文章获得新的见解亚当·兰扎
we got our report tonight from our national correspondent Kate snow
我们得到了我们今晚的报告从我们国家的记者凯特雪
Adam Lanza killed 20 young children 6th Ave in self and its mother
亚当·兰扎在自我和其母亲杀害了20名年轻的孩子第六大道
how does Peter Lanza live without
如何彼得·兰扎活不下去
it's incredibly difficult is full of sadness video only wishes he could go back in time and change it on 6
这是令人难以置信的困难是充满悲情的视频只希望他能回到过去，并在6改变它
Peter Lanza sought out Andrew Solomon after reading his book far from the tree in which Solomon chapter about the parents of children who commit unsinkable crimes
彼得·兰扎找到了安德鲁·所罗门从树上远读他的书后，所罗门章关于孩子是谁犯下的罪行不沉的父母
the feel like he's to blame it until I choose to blame he said even with all the information of simpatico there since then he doesn't see how he could possibly have seen it coming
感觉就像他责怪它，直到我选择责备他说即使有和蔼可亲那里所有的信息，因为当时他没有看到他怎么可能看到它的到来
Solomon interview Peter Lanza over 25 hours the father painting a picture of a little boy who loved hiking calling him just a normal little weird kid
所罗门采访彼得·兰扎超过25小时的父亲画的谁爱远足称他只是一个普通的怪异的孩子小一小男孩的图片
at 13 he was diagnosed with Aspergers Syndrome form of autism is divorced parents work for years to get him help Peter Lanza now thanks for the ass burger diagnosis mast deeper issues
13，他被诊断出患有阿斯伯格综合症自闭症形式的离婚父母工作多年，让他帮助彼得兰扎现在感谢您的屁股汉堡诊断肥大更深层次的问题
lots of people have aspergers and or autism and don't commit or her with a cat
很多人有阿斯伯格和自闭症或不提交或她与猫
absolutely in parents fail to realize emperor of the doctor said to realize how much darkness neva was brewing in him because they were distracted by the autism
绝对的父母没有认识到医生的皇帝说，实现涅瓦河是多么的黑暗酝酿他，因为他们是由自闭症分心
has Adam groom or withdrawing is father says his ex wife Nancy Lanza wanted everyone to think everything was okay she didn't know she was communicating with only by email is windows covered in black plastic I didn't understand the atom was drifting away Peter Lanza told Solomon
已亚当新郎或撤销的父亲说，他的前妻南希·兰扎希望每个人都觉得一切都还不错，她不知道，她只通过电子邮件是覆盖在黑色的塑料窗我不明白的原子是渐行渐远彼得·兰扎是沟通告诉所罗门
continue to write out of birthday cards the last song his son two years before the Newtown shooting
继续前两年的现代城拍摄写出来的生日贺卡的最后一首歌曲他的儿子
guns in the house but he wasn't concerned
枪在家里，但他并不担心
he describe teaching Adam to drive is a data within as possible following person I ever met is it in Everett hurt me that he would break the rules around the town
他形容教学亚当驱动是尽可能下面的人，我见过它是在埃弗雷特内的数据伤害我，他会打破周围的市镇规则
Peter Lanza wishes now he push harder to see his son even if it had caused fights it couldn't be worse than what did happen you can't get any more evil Lanza told Solomon adding he wished his son had never been born to sync Adam Hayden
彼得·兰扎希望现在他推很难看到他的儿子，即使它已造成打架它可能不会比没发生什么更糟糕你不能得到任何更邪恶兰扎告诉所罗门增加，他希望他的儿子从未出生到亚当同步海登
his parents me and I think animated everyone I mean he killed his mother when is fathers did I know that he was shot me in a heartbeat if you have the opportunity
他的父母给我，我觉得动画大家，我的意思是他杀害了他的母亲时，父亲才知道他被枪杀我的心跳，如果你有机会
is it the reason that he shot 94 times was one for each others pants for Nancy lens for Ryan wants from me and wants for himself
这是他出手94次的原因是为每个人的裤子​​南希镜头瑞安想要从我这里，并希望为自己
Peter Lanza has met with to a victim's family that has offered to meet them all he told Andrew he wants it all parents to be afraid of the fact that this could happen to them on a website with posted what he says are lessons Brian for parents
彼得·兰扎会见了以已提出以满足他们所有的，他告诉安德鲁，他希望这一切的父母害怕的事实，这可能会发生在自己身上的一个网站，一个受害者的家属张贴他说什么教训布莱恩的父母
maybe the most disturbing store in recent memory thanks for your reporting tonight still have for us tonight as the search intensifies for this
也许在你今晚报告最近的记忆感谢最令人不安的店今晚仍然有我们作为搜索的加剧对本
missing jetliner how it is with 2014 technology that is left without a trace
失踪客机它是如何与2014年的技术，剩下的无影无踪
Rebecca's promise with more on this disappearance of flight 370 and the question that is a merge from the start when we first learn about a Friday night how is it possible a wide body aircraft has disappeared without an electronic paying without a locator beacon without
丽贝卡的承诺与更偏重于飞行370这样消失，这是从一开始就合并当我们第一次了解一个周五晚上怎么可能一个宽体飞机早已消失无电子不带定位信标不付款的问题
price of any sort NBC Stephanie Gosk tonight on the limitations of our technology
我们的技术的局限性任何形式的NBC斯蒂芬妮Gosk今晚的价格
the West locations of Malaysia Airlines flight 372
马来西亚航空公司飞行372西地区
who is over the South China Sea after that
谁是在中国南海后
John Casey is a former international pilot for American Airlines
约翰·凯西​​是前国际飞行员为美国航空公司
the only way in the world where they are going to be able to look at your position is 5 million warrior last position was in which an exposition who is predicted to be
在世界上，他们将能够查看您的位置，唯一的办法就是500万勇士的最后一个位置是在哪一个博览会谁被预测为
Radar only tracks Plains winair overland and lease within 120 miles of land
雷达只能跟踪平原WINAIR陆路和120公里范围内的土地租用
take a flight from New York on its way to Chicago radar can pinpoint the plains location at all times how long is 2&a half hour trip 7 different control towers track a flight
从纽约的道路上雷达芝加哥航班可以在任何时候找准位置，平原7个不同的控制塔多长时间为2和一个半小时的行程跟踪航班
pics of from New York to London beyond 120 miles offshore the play music GPS to determine its exact location and then
从纽约的照片到伦敦以外120英里离岸播放音乐的GPS来确定其准确位置，然后
how to communicate does coordinates to controllers on the ground round the world the gap between communications can be as long as an hour FlightAware provide live tracking for more than 75040 today
如何沟通并协调对地面控制环游世界通信之间的间隙可只要一小时FlightAware超过75040提供实时跟踪今天
does exist to track lanes every second of every flight but it's not easy solution
确实存在跟踪车道每次飞行的每一秒钟，但它不是简单的解决方案
the ward choir a lot more satellites and less expensive transmission of data on satellite which is it really on the horizon it doesn't seem viable
病房合唱团更大量的卫星和卫星数据的更便宜变速器，是不是真的在地平线上它似乎并不可行
what happened to Malaysia Airlines flight 370 remains a mystery
发生了什么事马来西亚航空公司航班370仍是一个谜
does it make sense in 2014
是否有意义，在2014年
scratching their heads
挠头
where it went down is only for the battle is still have to figure out why Stephanie Gosk NBC News New York
它下楼只为战斗还是要弄清楚为什么斯蒂芬妮Gosk NBC新闻纽约
take a break your back in a moment with the story of a man who actually got to drive a Ford with the original
走一会儿休息一下你的背部与一个男人究竟是谁拿到驾驶福特与原来的故事
Henry Ford
亨利·福特
some remembrances tonight's starting with William clay Ford who died over the weekend he was the last surviving grandchild of Henry Ford and once famously steer a car while driving in his famous grandfathers lap it was a el Grande a Navy veteran who married a member of the Firestone family
有些回忆今晚的首发与威廉·克莱·福特谁死在周末，他亨利·福特的最后幸存的孙子和曾经有句名言引导一辆车，而驾驶在他著名的祖父搭接它是一个昆内特拉格兰一个海军退伍军人谁娶了凡世通会员家庭
while he owns the Detroit Lions ever ran the company the Bears his family name is older brother Henry Ford the second instead it was a company Mandela major stockholders served on the board of Ford Motor for 57 years
而他拥有的底特律雄狮队以往任何时候都经营这家公司，熊家人的名字是哥哥亨利·福特第二相反，它是一个公司的曼德拉大股东担任福特汽车的董事会57年
William clay Ford was 88 years old
威廉·克莱·福特88岁
Garnier has died the man who served with a man Easy Company of the 2nd battalion 101st airborne in world war 2
卡尼尔已经死了谁担任了一个男人的第二个营的中易公司在世界战争2第101空降男人
new hamburger as Wild Bill Maher exploits were popularized in the HBO miniseries Band of Brothers in which he was played by the actor Frank John Hughes rescuing a fellow soldier was awarded the Silver Star 2 bronze stars on the Purple Heart
新汉堡作为野生比尔马哈尔战功被普及了HBO的迷你剧兄弟连中，他的角色由演员弗兰克·约翰·休斯抢救战友被授予银星2铜星的紫心
South Philadelphia native Wild Bill Guarnere was 90 years old
南费城本地野生比尔Guarnere是90岁
when we come back tonight one upside what's been a brutal winter
我们回来的时候，今晚一个好处什么是一个残酷的冬天
most the need for speed on a frozen sheet of ice
最需要的速度在冰的冻结表
finally here tonight it was in the 70's in the Dakotas this weekend only to fall 40 degrees with the next front
终于来了，今晚它是在70年代在达科他州本周末仅下降40度与下前
and the East Coast go to get at least one more snow storm before this is all over for those in the thick of it in Spanish miserable winter from the Great Lakes
和东海岸去获得至少一个或多个雪灾之前，这一切都结束对于那些在它的厚西班牙语悲惨的冬天从五大湖
show my chest still frozen over but that in itself is rhere good news for one exotic beautiful and thrilling sport
秀我的胸部仍然冻结了，但是这本身就是一个异国情调的美丽和惊险刺激的运动rhere好消息
tonight NBC's Katie Turner reports on the ice boulders who are having a great seas
今晚谁是有一个很大的海洋冰巨石NBC的凯蒂·特纳报告
cold March morning the frozen Hudson River was transformed into a playground
寒冷的三月清晨冰封哈得逊河变成了一个游乐场
that is when you can get it at all it's been a decade since the ice with a foot 2nd strong enough to hold
那就是当你可以得到它在所有它，因为用一只脚冰过了十年二强到足以容纳
big boats on the Hudson nearly a century the rocket sales built in 1888 the rocket was once the fastest thing on the planet body like a crossbow with stupid sales 4310 metal plate
在Hudson近一个世纪建于1888年，火箭销量火箭一度以最快的事情在这个星球上身体像愚蠢销售4310金属板弩大船
such a marvel Thomas Edison filmed in 1905 what's it like to see it
这样的奇迹托马斯·爱迪生摄制于1905年，它是什么喜欢看它
Pinterest work on the so hard
就这么难Pinterest的工作
in the basement a new jerseys North Shrewsbury ice boat and yacht club bump old sled years of meticulous restoration peace in the craft back together
在地下室的新球衣北什鲁斯伯里冰船和游艇俱乐部凹凸旧雪橇多年的工艺一丝不苟恢复和平重新走到一起
don't have to be just right they have to be perfect for stew need a whole lot of cold then some snow then some rain even more colds
没有要恰到好处他们必须是完美的，炖需要一大堆的冷再下点雪再下点雨就更容易感冒
companies in almost human ever happened to be off of stubborn
公司几乎在人类经历过被关闭的倔强
the band chasing a strong wind in hard freeze on this river for generation
乐队追逐强风硬冻结这条河的一代
when every every pull off the ropes every right to be your last
当每一个每一个拉断的绳索一切权利是你的最后